[{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980229136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":16058,"timeElapsed":41966},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980239271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":10134,"timeElapsed":52101},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980245328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6055,"timeElapsed":58158},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980250919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5591,"timeElapsed":63749},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980258728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7807,"timeElapsed":71558},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980266921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":8192,"timeElapsed":79751},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980272552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5630,"timeElapsed":85382},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980276280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3727,"timeElapsed":89110},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980278863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2583,"timeElapsed":91693},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980312256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":31742,"timeElapsed":125086},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980317497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":5240,"timeElapsed":130327},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980320743,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3245,"timeElapsed":133573},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980324689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3945,"timeElapsed":137519},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980329047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4358,"timeElapsed":141877},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980333064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4016,"timeElapsed":145894},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":361749,"timeElapsed":507645},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2439,"timeElapsed":510085},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2721,"timeElapsed":512806},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980706344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5119,"timeElapsed":519174},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980716623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":10278,"timeElapsed":529453},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980732983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":16359,"timeElapsed":545813},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980739448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":6464,"timeElapsed":552278},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980745807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":6358,"timeElapsed":558637},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980752655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":6847,"timeElapsed":565485},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980756448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3792,"timeElapsed":569278},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4807,"timeElapsed":574086},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980764143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2886,"timeElapsed":576973},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980769240,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5096,"timeElapsed":582070},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980779959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":9296,"timeElapsed":592789},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980784223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4262,"timeElapsed":597053},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980787087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2863,"timeElapsed":599917},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980790424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3336,"timeElapsed":603254},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6519,"timeElapsed":609774},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980805543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":8597,"timeElapsed":618373},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980808839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3295,"timeElapsed":621669},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3584,"timeElapsed":625254},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980816095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3670,"timeElapsed":628925},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980824576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7191,"timeElapsed":637406},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980829271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4694,"timeElapsed":642101},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980832087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2815,"timeElapsed":644917},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980837167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5079,"timeElapsed":649997},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980841744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4576,"timeElapsed":654574},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980844895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3150,"timeElapsed":657725},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980847671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2775,"timeElapsed":660501},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980850071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2399,"timeElapsed":662901},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980853063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2991,"timeElapsed":665893},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980861696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7352,"timeElapsed":674526},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980866576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4879,"timeElapsed":679406},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980871391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4814,"timeElapsed":684221},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980876543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5151,"timeElapsed":689373},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3159,"timeElapsed":692533},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980884103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4399,"timeElapsed":696933},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980886974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2871,"timeElapsed":699804},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980889479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2503,"timeElapsed":702309},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980892095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2615,"timeElapsed":704925},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981064599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":171429,"timeElapsed":877428},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981067287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2687,"timeElapsed":880117},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981072511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":5223,"timeElapsed":885341},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981075679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3167,"timeElapsed":888509},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981078319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2639,"timeElapsed":891149},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981080703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2383,"timeElapsed":893533},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981083126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2423,"timeElapsed":895956},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981085367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2239,"timeElapsed":898197},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981087679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2311,"timeElapsed":900508},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981256296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":167519,"timeElapsed":1069126},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981260038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3742,"timeElapsed":1072868},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981263998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3959,"timeElapsed":1076828},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981268430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4431,"timeElapsed":1081260},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981273374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4943,"timeElapsed":1086204},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981280616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":7240,"timeElapsed":1093445},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981285814,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5198,"timeElapsed":1098644},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981290512,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4696,"timeElapsed":1103342},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981293192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2679,"timeElapsed":1106021},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981295574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2382,"timeElapsed":1108404},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981302656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":5951,"timeElapsed":1115486},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981307758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5102,"timeElapsed":1120588},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981314144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":6384,"timeElapsed":1126974},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981317582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3438,"timeElapsed":1130412},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981320518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2935,"timeElapsed":1133348},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981325551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":5032,"timeElapsed":1138381},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981328454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2902,"timeElapsed":1141284},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981330422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":1967,"timeElapsed":1143252},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981332974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2551,"timeElapsed":1145804},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981338078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4030,"timeElapsed":1150908},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981339902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1823,"timeElapsed":1152732},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981341942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2039,"timeElapsed":1154772},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981343886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1943,"timeElapsed":1156716},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981346854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2967,"timeElapsed":1159684},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981348774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1919,"timeElapsed":1161604},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981352511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3736,"timeElapsed":1165341},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981354398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1886,"timeElapsed":1167228},{"subjectID":"rox7zvdeun","prolificID":"56a90c96119265000c6e134d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f246709d0172ba49f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981356422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2023,"timeElapsed":1169252}]